<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Karcis</string>
    <string name="info">I N F O</string>
    <string name="buy">BUY</string>
    <string name="preman"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nAfter three years, the business of Muslihat, who has retired as a thug, has a problem. Sales decline. Muslihat also faces new problems when Safira, her only daughter, grows up in adolescence and begins to be visited by boys. A bigger problem: frictions between his former subordinates. Written by filmindonesia.or.id</string>
    <string name="star"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nSeasoned musician Jackson Maine (Bradley Cooper) discovers-and falls in love with-struggling artist Ally (Gaga). She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer - until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally`s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons. Written by Warner Bros.</string>
    <string name="bird"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nIn the wake of an unknown global terror, a mother must find the strength to flee with her children down a treacherous river in search of safety. Due to unseen deadly forces, the perilous journey must be made blindly. Directed by Emmy winner Susanne Bier, Bird Box is a thriller starring Academy Award winner Sandra Bullock, John Malkovich, Sarah Paulson, and Trevante Rhodes. Written by Netflix</string>
    <string name="hunter"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nA U.S. submarine, the USS Tampa Bay, vanishes while shadowing a Russian Akula-class submarine in the Arctic. Rear Admiral John Fisk sends a Virginia-class submarine, the USS Arkansas, under the command of newly-promoted and unorthodox Commander Joe Glass to investigate. At the same time, a Navy SEAL team under the command of Lieutenant Bill Beaman is sent in to discreetly observe a Russian naval base. When they arrive at the naval base, they witness defense minister Dmitri Durov conducting a coup d`etat and taking Russian President Zakarin prisoner, and swiftly realize that Durov intends to trigger a war..</string>
    <string name="glass"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nAfter pursuing Kevin Wendell Crumb and the multiple identities that reside within. David Dunn finds himself locked in a mental hospital alongside his archenemy, Elijah Price and must contend with a psychiatrist who is out to prove the trio do not actually possess superhuman abilities Written by vsuperkuns</string>
    <string name="dragon"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nAs Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccups reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind. Written by JC Jamison</string>
    <string name="spiderman"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nMiles Morales is a New York teen struggling with school, friends and, on top of that, being the new Spider-Man. When he comes across Peter Parker, the erstwhile saviour of New York, in the multiverse, Miles must train to become the new protector of his city. Written by Tom Daly</string>
    <string name="robinhood"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nA war-hardened crusader Robin of Loxley (Taron Egerton) and his Moorish commander (Jamie Foxx) mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.</string>
    <string name="bumblebee"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nOn Cybertron, the Autobots, led by Optimus Prime, are on the verge of losing the Great Cybertronian War to their enemies, the Decepticons, and begin making preparations to leave the planet. The Decepticons led by Shockwave, Soundwave and Starscream ambush them during the evacuation, and Optimus sends a young scout, B-127, to Earth in order to set up a base of operations where the Autobots can regroup. B-127 reaches Earth alone in 1987, crash-landing in California and disrupting a training exercise being conducted by Sector 7, a secret government agency that monitors extraterrestrial activity on Earth. Sector 7 agent Colonel Jack Burns presumes B-127 to be a hostile invader and attacks, driving B-127 into the forest, where he is then ambushed by the Decepticon Blitzwing. When B-127 refuses to reveal Optimus whereabouts, Blitzwing spitefully tears out his voice-box and damages his memory core. B-127 manages to destroy Blitzwing before collapsing from his wounds. Before entering stasis,... Written by Paramount Pictures</string>
    <string name="aquaman"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nArthur Curry, half human half from Atlantis, goes on a trip of a lifetime. Not only does this adventure compel him to come to terms with his real identity, but it also forces him to discover whether he is entirely worthy of fulfilling his own destiny: becoming a king. Written by Domingo Alvarez</string>
    <string name="venom"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nAfter a faulty interview with the Life Foundation ruins his career, former reporter Eddie Brocks life is in pieces. Six months later, he comes across the Life Foundation again, and he comes into contact with an alien symbiote and becomes Venom, a parasitic antihero.</string>
    <string name="endgame"><b>Storyline</b>\n\nAs the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment, the fate of Earth and existence has never been more uncertain. Written by Marvel Studios</string>

</resources>
